Bitcoin hit its first real resistance at
around 88,000 American dollars after
pumping 45%
this quarter. Quite the move. Many
calling for 90 and above right now.
We're going to talk about that and
everything else that's driving markets
and the news today. Of course, we have
Andrew and Tilman, but because you guys
don't really like them that much, we
also brought someone you do like, which
is Gary Cardone. You guys don't like me
either. It's fine. Let's go.
That's dope.
>> Let's go.
>> Good morning everybody. Happy Tuesday.
It is dawn here in New York City as you
can see. Um, oh, look at that view. Look
at that wolf. I made that on chat GPT
this morning. Not going to lie. I
vibecoded a new studio background. Do
the other one. Do the other one. Yeah.
Look at that in the window. All right,
I'm going to go ahead and bring on
Andrew, Gary, and Tilman. Uh, dude, the
AI is amazing. Seriously, I did that
this morning. I'm not saying it's that
great, but I have Grockbot now, too. And
I was like, whip up a dollar cost
averaging calculator for Bitcoin to show
the history of dollar cost averaging at
any point. And I forgot I did it. And
then it sent me a video of it like
clicking through and showing me all the
things that it does.
>> Yeah, it's uh it
>> it's going to meaningfully change how we
do things and what we do and when we do
it and where we do it a year from now.
There's going to be a lot a lot of
changes especially in finance. Lot of
changing in finance coming to the guys
that uh put on a suit and tie every day
and uh and and act.
>> This show is going to be for Grockbots.
>> Yeah. Right. Right.
>> Gary, what's up, man?
>> What's up, buddy?
>> How you doing? How are you?
>> I'm awesome, man. I am awesome.
>> Very smiley today. You seem happy. I
think you just froze on us again,
though.
>> Sweet. Frozen. Gary is a It's a killer
way to start the show. You know what I
mean?
>> Frozen with a smile. Okay, so let's uh
we're going to just dive into some news
while Gary unfreezes himself.
>> Uh he's in the matrix stuck. Stop. Spot.
Bitcoin ETFs attracted nearly nine
billion on Monday. Ninth largest inflow
ever to be honest. That was
>> nine. But what?
>> Yeah, that that that's not a surprise.
Um we'll probably see a big number as
well uh come through today. Um you know,
I think we're going to see big numbers
happen uh for the next couple weeks. The
interesting thing about that nearly 1
billion is, you know, not half of or
more of it came from IBID. only 380
million came from IBIT. It was it was
spread across, you know, the top five.
Also extremely interesting, Morgan
Stanley did 61.7 million. That's the
biggest inflow they've ever had since
inception by double, right? Their
biggest number on any given day was 30
million. 61.7.
Um, that's a that's a that's a big
number. Now, that's all demand from
Friday. So, that's Friday demand.
showing up on the books for Monday. So,
we'll see what happens uh today based on
>> usually the big IBIT numbers we can
point to and say that's
>> option stuff, you know, people
>> option stuff and like it's all on IBIT
because people are shorting, you know,
the futures and whatever, but if it's
spread out that real this might be the
first time we go, wow, people really
bought a lot of this stuff.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Fidelity had big inflows.
ARC actually had big inflows. Bitwise,
big inflows. And again, Morgan Stanley
had the biggest inflow day that they've
ever had since since they launched their
spot Bitcoin ETF. So that's retail
demand, right? Like that's what jumped
out to me is that Morgan Stanley number
is absolutely retail demand. That's
wealth management retail demand jumping
into an asset. So important to note and
and probably is a harbinger of what the
next, let's call it 30 to 90 days look
like.
Hey Andrew, do you think that's um
public that is asking the investment
bankers for Bitcoin or do you think the
investment bankers are saying, "Hey, you
need an allocation?"
>> Yeah, it's probably Yeah, it's it's
probably 6040 they're asking for it and
40 that they're talking about it. So,
great question. I know a lot of Morgan
Stanley advisers. I've got a close
friend who's one in Columbus, Ohio. And
what I know about him and his team, I
highly doubt they're going out and
saying, "Hey everybody, you need to add
Bitcoin to your portfolio." I I I I
doubt that he's doing that. But I I
would bet that he's getting it from uh
his clients. It's saying, "Yep, yeah,
let's let's do that. Let's add a a small
allocation."
>> There's no greater marketing for Bitcoin
ETFs than Bitcoin price simply going up
and being back news for being above
80,000. Right. That said, I would say
that Morgan Stanley probably might be
skewed slightly more towards adviserss
because they've recently put their sales
team on it since they launched.
>> Right. So, I I I think you're right. I
think 90% of them aren't. But I bet
there are some Morgan Stanley advisers
now who have gotten the uh message to go
out and sell the thing, which is why
Morgan Stanley created an ETF when
they're not really sure in the first
place. I've spoken to Amy Oldenberg this
summer who's the head of you know crypto
or whatever at Morgan Stanley and she
said that was actively going to start
happening but I mean 40 to 80 is huge
like you said or 30 to 60 whatever it
was them doubling but still you know
that's a
>> 6% of the daily inflows on the Bitcoin
>> yeah no no doubt but but again at Morgan
Stanley that that is as pure retail
demand as we're going to see like like
that is and again I I mentioned it
before. The Morgan Stanley spot Bitcoin
ETF has seen zero dollars of outflows.
Not a none. Zero. Right. So that crowd
jumping into that asset that is a that
is a stick to it. I've made a decision
to be at one or two or 3% allocation in
my portfolio and I'm not coming off of
it. um and you know back at it after the
after the summer and you know making
allocations. We're September 22nd people
have probably had their Q3 or going into
Q4 portfolio review and so you're seeing
some of this movement, right? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean so just to add to this and
Gary, I just want your kind of general
thoughts on the move after this, but the
average Bitcoin ETF holder is back above
water for the first time since January.
The rally this morning has Bitcoin above
our estimated ETF cost basis of 81,722
per coin obviously much higher now. I
mean you see these kind of things all
the time with Bitcoin pumps, right? ETF
holders are back in profit. Sailor way
back in profit all you know the he had
to go to zero. Now he's a genius again
because he's billions of dollars in
profit by we know how it all literally
just like rotates with the price. But
but Gary, you know, like you and I would
talk kind of a lot about Bitcoin price
action, sentiment, all these things. Uh
I haven't even talked to you since I
think the move up. Were you surprised by
the move up? You know, uh did you
anticipate lower still? Do you still
anticipate lower? Do you think there's a
real move? I mean, how are you just
framing this right now?
>> Well, look, you know, when Sailor
stopped selling, I mean, we have a price
here that like sailors not selling, not
buying. Uh when he started selling, I
thought, okay, we might be reaching the
end. the Satsuma
implosion the other day.
>> Like I said months ago, hey, all of
these strategy companies have to sell
their Bitcoin before we can go anywhere.
Like 180 companies, I think four of them
maybe keep their position. But you got
600,000 Bitcoin that need to come back.
600 Bitcoin from Satsuma came back in.
That's good. We have a lot of pressure
on this market and it's holding here.
Now, I was bearish all summer because
quite frankly, I wanted to buy more
Bitcoin at 57,000 or below.
And if the market's gonna allow me to
talk it down, while while Sailor could
couldn't say anything, and you know, the
BMNR guys on his back feet, I mean,
everybody's struggling. I'm like, hey,
if this market's going to allow X
Twitter spaces to for me to just pound
on it, the worst case is my twin brother
buys a lot of Bitcoin he couldn't have
bought otherwise. too will figure out
how thick this market really is. Like is
this really a market? Is it an X market
or is it a real market? And I want a
real market. I am so tired of the X
spaces Twitter point to Bitcoin holders
thinking that they control anything
here.
>> And so to me, this is why I came into
this market. I've had to wait eight or
nine years, but Wall Street's taking
over and it's awesome.
>> Yeah. Absolutely
awesome. I have been made fun of on my
strateg STRC package. I'd love to take
somebody through this. I could have
bought $98,000 Bitcoin six, eight, nine
months ago. And uh instead, I bought
STRC and I've been paid $63,000 a month.
>> Yeah.
>> 63. I I've acquired 12 Bitcoin
>> and I'm still going to be able to move
from STRC at 99.5. That's what I paid
for it. As soon as it hits 99.5 or 100,
I'm gonna move into cash. I've collected
all that money. And if I have to buy
$80,000 Bitcoin, this has been an
awesome trade for me.
>> Yeah,
>> I've made $750,000
on STRC while I didn't know what the
market was doing. I was confused.
>> And by the way, that was without you
buying it below par.
>> Uh yeah. And I bought it
and holding it. like you didn't you
didn't buy it at 75 or 80 or 85 where
there could
>> I bought it near par and I was never
worried about that people are like hey
he's getting liquidated I'm like nobody
called me from the bank nobody cared
like dude the guy's getting 11 and a
half% with a really cool tax allocation.
So for me, having all these tools and
being a Bitcoiner and being able to
arbitrage between Wall Street and
digital assets, dude, it is the ultimate
option tool and and and why Bitcoiners
wouldn't want Wall Street and although
to be able to reach in there and go,
"Hey, I'm going to go grab this." Now, I
could have just sat in cash. That would
have been horrible. I could have sat in
Bitcoin at 95 grand and gone all the way
to 65. Right. I have some of that, by
the way. I have some of that, right?
Yeah.
>> So to me,
Bitcoin's actually maturing.
>> Yeah.
>> And that to me is what has to happen. We
have to mature. And you know, I heard
somebody say the other day, hey, 7% of
the the world is allocated to Bitcoin.
There isn't a chance in hell it's 7%.
It's more like seven.
>> Yeah, that's the truth. Okay.
>> Of the world is allocated to any assets.
>> Right.
>> Right. Right. Right. like assets period.
I think there's more than 93% of the
world that's uh
>> living paycheck to paycheck.
>> Now, I do think we have a lot of wood to
chop and that that's what I would like
to talk about. Hey, this thing is not
going to go straight up. Okay? Anyone
sitting here listening to crypto bros
going, "It's going to 147 tomorrow
morning." Dude, relax. Okay? Talk to
experts and buy Bitcoin at the right
price. Don't chase Bitcoin. I love the
idea that it's that it's raising the
floor of the ranges. You know what I
mean? Like that's kind of how I view it.
And the last one didn't it only lasted
four weeks or whatever that kind of 70s
to 80s or, you know, mid70s to low 80s.
Now maybe we'll range from mid70s to
mid, you know, to 90. I don't know. I I
don't see what's going to make it
skyrocket to your point. Uh and that's
why I use arch public
whatever. But I can tell you as
everybody knows here just as evidence
because Gary you said what you were
doing. I'll tell you what I was doing. I
did buy SDRC at 100 93 85 74 not your
same size and now have ridden it because
I understand I'm getting paid a dividend
on 100 regardless of when I buy it. So I
you know and listen I was literally
being accused of being a sailor paid
shill. I don't know if people remember
this at the bottom. I was defending
strategy on math and data not on like
personality. just saying like you can't
use words like we'll be liquidated or
bankrupt or insolvent when you have
850,000 Bitcoin and yeah here we are
>> that was ridiculous. Okay, people saying
that I'm like I don't even think you
believe in Bitcoin. If you think Sailor
can go down with 800,000 Bitcoin, you
are not you understand a very different
Bitcoin than I do.
>> Yeah, but I just so I bought a bunch of
STRC but with the bulk of my portfolio I
was just using Arch Public and buying
Bitcoin and I don't know we haven't
updated in a long time. I bought Ethan
Salana at much smaller amounts as well.
I am as of this week I am way in profit
>> and not only that it sold a bunch then
bought I got panicked you know I was
like why am I selling Bitcoin I want to
hold forever because it sold it at like
you know 80 and then it bought again at
just yesterday at like 88 and I'm sure
now if it dips to 85 it's going to buy
more but my cost basis actually went
down when it started selling about four
three or 4 thousand more dollars in that
process cuz my cost basis was maybe like
83 84 and now it's 79 or 80.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, I let me let me jump into
>> want to get into arch public, but that
was my strategy. My strategy through
this whole dip was just this was it. I
started at the dead top and here we are
still 30% off the highs and I'm in
profit on all of it.
>> Well, and you wanted to spend all of it
at 126, which would have you know h
emotion is the enemy of trading and
retail is riddled with emotion. Like one
of the things I'll point out about
Gary's journey that I've appreciated is
that, you know, he's been managing dry
powder as much as anything. Like I I've
seen all of his posts go back go back to
when you were selling silver and you
were posting about getting rid of, you
know, depreciatory assets, your
vehicles, your like all of the the game
is about the opportunity cost that you
can either be patient to take advantage
of or that you're not and you miss the
boat on. And Bitcoin rewards patient
people with dry powder that have
conviction. That's just the bottom line.
And that's the opposite of what most
people who have been in the space live
according to. And Wall Street is the
exact opposite. That's all they live
according to. It's about wealth
preservation. It's about having the dry
powder when they need it to make the
appropriate move into the asset class.
And that's not typically at the dead
bottom. It's typically the middle of the
trade that they really want to take
because that's the most risk-free trade
that you can make with the highest
upside. And you're just seeing like an
evolution of the markets. To Gary's
point, Bitcoin is maturing. What did
this summer represent to me? It
represented a changing of the guard. We
had the cold card hack that literally
disrupted the very core uh pun intended
of the Bitcoin community. Um and and I I
think that you know you then you
extrapolate all of the other headlines
that have happened this summer. They all
have one common theme attached to them.
It's like the people who got us here are
not the people to take the lead going
forward. And the people who have really
focused on integrating this
systematically into our financial
system. Those are the people that are
driving the narrative going forward. And
those are the people that understand
what yield potential is and what
volatility potential is. and they're not
so attracted to the long-term bet of the
appreciation. What they're attracted to
is what Gary got after earlier, which is
like depth of liquidity in the market
and how much volatility opportunity
presents itself. If you can capture a
very volatile market with a lot of depth
of liquidity and global structure behind
it, there is more yield potential than
than there is upside potential. Uh and
you don't have to be, you know, a wizard
to look through your crystal ball to
find it. you're literally just playing
the ups and downs systematically against
the rest of the people who are driven by
emotion. And I think that's what we've
seen over the last 90 days as much as
anything is like the real buyers are
stepping in and they're not chasing big
green candles. They're actually waiting
for the red candles. They're waiting for
the retest and then they're like, "Okay,
this is a prudent time to allocate
capital." And those are not soft, weak
hands. Those are like the most diamond
hands that exist. They don't ever have
to sell.
>> Yeah. A couple things to to add to that.
Um, first of all, as per Gary's comments
about, you know, exsanity associated
with Sailor, I think they've called 25
of the last zero Sailor liquidations uh
over the past six years. I remember the
the liquidation, you know, conversation,
you know, having to do with Sailor at
13K. I remember before at 8K.
>> Yeah. assuming he was going to get
liquidated and it went to 15 and he sold
a few and bought back the next week at
17 and by the way dead ass bottom of the
market.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and so you know again
conversations on X um can be interesting
and fill a little bit of time but they
they have meaningfully adjusted again
Wall Street absolutely has taken over.
Um the other thing too based on the fact
that that Bitcoin is a meaningful asset
across uh the financial system now
Bitcoin will outperform broader markets
but it's not going to outperform four to
5x to one. It's not going to do that
over the next 3 to 5 years. It will
outperform 1.75
to one or 1.95
to one. And that's really really
meaningful, right? But you if you're
expecting a 4 one 3 one, you know, 200%
year over the next 3 years, you need to
you need to make a mental adjustment.
You know, Black Rockck's product coupled
with their options, I'm telling you
right now, will not allow a 250%
year in Bitcoin over the next three
years. Well, even just the reality, just
the truth. You may not like it, but that
is the truth. I'm just letting
>> Andrew, to your point, and to Gary's
point earlier, not only will they not
allow that, but they're not going to
allow a continuation move to to keep
going after we've been up 40 something%
in the last 2 weeks or whatever it is. I
mean, you're talking about that is the
play. If you missed this last move, it's
not time to jump in the boat right now.
You just you just literally saw a move
off of the VWAP that is three standard
deviations above any move that we've
had. We've seen like a massive amount of
volatility. So, here's what people
typically get trapped into thinking.
They go, "Oh, we're at 85 and the high
is 126. That means I'm almost guaranteed
to go to 126." And they load the boat
right now. What I would argue is that
when you have a 40 plus% move, you're
much we are 90% more likely to go back
down to 75 than we are to go back up to
95. Like say take the same 10,000 range
above the current price below and above.
What is the probability that it goes
down 10% versus goes up 10% from right
here? And it's not an emotional
feelingbased question. It's like what's
the probability of a continuation event
going from 40% plus in a twoe period to
a 50%. How big of an anomaly move would
that be? Not saying it couldn't happen,
but people don't adjust their risk based
upon the existing percentage that we've
moved. And that's just a major fallacy
in their investment thesis in my
opinion. like that you you're supposed
to be placing capital based upon the
riskreward ratio that presents itself at
the time of purchase. The riskreward
ratios materially changed over the last
3 days than it was 3 days ago. So if you
are taking the same purchasing power
into today's market as you were 3 days
ago, I would call you an unsophisticated
investor. That's not what Wall Street
does is the point. Uh and that's not
what all the big heavyweights are doing
now. there there's a riskadjusted curve
that they always want to go back to
period.
>> Yeah. I mean there's a lot of reasons to
believe that this move is slightly
overheated, right? You know 82 we were
going straight to 90 and we went back to
75, right? And you know that that was a
reasonable opportunity. I mean you got
fear and greed here is what uh
>> this can stay here for a very long time
but yeah we've hit extreme greed for the
first time here. You know people are
excited again. the Morgan Stanley
advisers calling. Uh, usually I'm I
haven't looked at open interest, but I'm
going to assume that it's piling up big
time. That said, I will once again say
and and you know, Gary, I didn't really
get to your opinion, I guess, on the
market moving forward, but there has
been a very clear sort of regime change
here. You know, like the the the things
that you're looking for to confirm are
there. So there's there's kind of like
there's the DCA people like us and
especially ones using tools, but if
you're trading, there's like two kinds
of people who have been playing this
market in my mind. Those the bottom
feeders who were trying to buy at 60,
maybe thought it was going lower, but
you were like pretty excited. You're
like, I'm trying to buy a bottom and the
confirmation people, you know, who are
waiting for a higher high or the 50 MA
on the weekly or whatever. Well, now
we're above everything, right? Here you
go. Bitcoin has reclaimed every one of
its long-term moving averages. We all
know that. If you take a look at the
chart, you can see, you know, that was
the higher high right there at 828. So
maybe the
proper way to frame this in my mind is
in a bare market, you were looking to
sell RIPS. Now you should be looking to
buy dips.
>> Mhm.
>> Is that an accurate
>> to your point on I I saw a post you made
about DCA and somebody said, "Hey, I'm
going to start DCA now." And you're
like, "Dude, you're missing the whole
point of DCA. You need a DCA when people
are vomiting."
>> What was that? And no hate. I think it
was Leia Halpern's brother. you know,
she's taking kind of a beating. And he
was like, "Oh, almost time to start
dollar cost averaging." And no, hey, I'm
just saying, but like now we're dollar
cost average at 90 instead of 60 because
we think we know something about the
market. Doesn't make much sense to me.
>> Yeah, it is. It is a uh you know,
everybody has an opinion on X. And
again, I I I think it's the most preient
point that that Gary can make is is it
it we're there. you know, Scott, you
you're there. It's a it's a place and a
and a you know, sort of a holding court
of ideas, but the truth of the matter is
is no different than what Micron does,
what Nvidia does, what Tesla does.
That's not all happening on X. It's it's
you're not getting meaningful outcomes
based on conversations on X spaces
associated with Microsoft stock. That
that that's not that's not what's going
on. and and we've moved into that space
with uh you know with with with Bitcoin.
The other thing too again Sailor is this
gargantuan figure in in Bitcoin and the
community and and for all the right
reasons he's done incredible stuff with
digital credit. Again, to Gary's point,
made a lot of money with that that dig
some of his digital credit products. But
outside of the Bitcoin community, you
know, I don't know how many uh money,
you know, 2020
uh talks that uh Sailor's doing. I I I I
don't know how many of those tradi
um conferences he's the headline speaker
at.
>> It was last year.
>> I don't know. you know it was last year
but but not this year right so
>> 2020
>> yes so it's it's there there are big
differences um but over time um again
Bitcoin is um you know will be an asset
that more and more people own in the
trady world it's just not where we'd
hoped it would be as of right now it
will be but again it just takes time it
>> I think that's all based upon the the
the lend the lending part of Bitcoin.
The narrative behind real estate. You
can say all you want about real estate
and how it's made so many millions of,
you know, million millionaires in
America. It's the backbone. It is. But
when you really peel back the onion, the
reason why it is is cuz it's one of the
most liquid assets that you can have
upside potential against. You can go to
any bank and pull a heliloc literally
the day after you close on a property
and they'll give you money against the
positive equity. We've systematically
made liquidity available attached to
real estate. When that can be said for
Bitcoin, I think you're going to see
more people come in because you're going
to be you're going to see lower rate
offerings. You're going to see rates
that are more attractive than any other
rate that you can get when the
collateral is Bitcoin. Period. The end.
Why? Well, because it's easier to
repossess. If you just stop there, it'll
be a cheaper rate. There's a lot of
other reasons, too. But just there, it's
going to be cheaper rate. Well, what
does that do? It ju just attracts people
to use it as collateral. And I think
that's really where the the breaking
point happens for like retail in America
is when you can go down to a bank and
you can go, I own a Bitcoin. And they
go, great, we'll give you a preferred
rate against a loan attached to it. Send
it to this wallet and you'll get the
money tomorrow. when we get there, it
will be a household name like we've
never dreamed it would be.
>> I I I wholeheartedly agree with that.
Okay. One day, the collateral value of
Bitcoin will be absolutely
the creme de la creme collateral.
>> Now, if you don't really understand
that, uh, then maybe you've been
spending too much time with some punks
in in spaces. Literally, I mean, I have
people go, they have 100 Bitcoin,
they're not doing something with it. I'm
like, I don't understand that. Okay, I'm
either going to borrow against it or I'm
going to lean against it. One or the
other. Now, the question is, can I
withstand? This is why the STRC product
was really cool. I'm borrowing from
Coinbase at 7 and a half%.
I'm borrowing from my bank at 5 and a
half and I'm getting paid 11 and a half.
>> Mhm.
>> Hell yeah. Well, and I've removed the
volatility from the underlying
commodity. And by the way, I now have a
lot of Bitcoin. I It allows me to be
more, shall we say, I'm not chasing the
redhead anymore. Like before when I came
in, I'm like, dude, I got to get 100
Bitcoin. I got to get 200 Bitcoin, you
know, and it doesn't matter. Price
doesn't matter. that. That is
ridiculous. Price absolutely matters,
man. Your entry price. If I'm buying
apartments with my brother, I care about
what their entry price is. The exit will
be easy if my entry price was correct.
>> Yep.
>> Well, that's where in any asset that's
where your money's made is the entry
price, right?
What you're doing is so important, man.
Because like it's hard to pick these
prices.
>> Well, I think it's start
>> Well, you should start with the notion
that you can't. I think that's what
people get a they start to fool
themselves. Even what you mentioned
earlier about like now's the time to
start dcaing.
That tells me you don't even understand
what DCAing is because DCAing is
predicated on one central thesis. I
can't time the market. Period. And if
you can't time the market, then you
don't try to time it with your DCA
strategy. Like it doesn't make any
sense. And I think systematically though
it gets very boring. And people have to
be honest with themselves. are not
chasing profits. They're chasing ego and
they want to be right and they want to
make the post. No different than we've
seen what was the guy that made $100
million this year and
>> that was last year. I think it was James
Win or whatever.
>> James Win. Everybody wants to be James
Win. No one wants to be Warren Buffett.
And and and that's just the nature of
like fame and everybody looking at you
going, "Look, he's a genius." I think we
all want that more than we actually want
to be wealthy. Uh because that's what I
see most of the actions being geared
towards.
>> Yeah. Listen, everybody wants to be
Scott Melker.
>> Warren Buffet never called me a
James Win did.
>> Wear it as a badge of honor. Wear it as
a badge of honor. Well, by the way,
interestingly enough, um, you know, I
think Warren just announced that he's
stepping down as the chairman, so he's
completely out.
>> Truth of the matter is, I don't know,
Warren Buffett, I think, uh, Birkshshire
was up something like 6.6 million%
during his tenure. Now, to be fair, that
was over, you know, 50, 60 years,
whatever it is, but that's a number. 6.6
million% is say is saying something. You
know, there's there there's value
associated with it. Um, and listen,
Warren Buffett was the king of entries,
right? He was absolutely the king of
entries. Um,
>> I think Warren I think he was a vulture
dude. Like a total vulture investor.
He's not like they say value. No, dude.
This guy's a vulture investor. He wants
to buy the bottom. He's going to squeeze
Goldman Sachs winning if he can.
Otherwise, he'll just sit around wait
for it.
>> Yeah.
>> How much How much uh powder do they have
on their balance sheet right now?
>> He started he started spending a little.
Not him. the new uh Bshire Hathway Cash.
Once again,
>> it's it's trillions. I know. I know it's
trillions. Um it's it's a it's a big
number
360. Bergkshire Hathway Cash fell from
397 billion to 360.
>> Okay. Billions in a single quarter, but
they they had I don't remember what they
did. They bought Apple. They bought
something. Uh
>> that's cash though, Andrew. So, they
have trillion dollar worth of buying
power.
>> Yeah, that's true. That's true.
Man,
>> to use it, right? 366 billion. How much
buying power do you have? I think banks
might listen.
>> Even the buying power, think about it
though, that you're measuring the buyer
power buying power up against $2
trillion as if they're buying assets
that don't need the liquidity. To Gary's
point, they're vultures. They're waiting
for the the company who is desperate. I
mean, look at the last look at the $30
billion hedge fund blow up and what
happened there. Citadel swept in. They
made they bought the book on pennies on
the dollar and then it immediately
rebounded and recovered. He who has the
gold makes the rules. And if you get to
a position where everyone knows you're
strapped for cash,
you're you're buying power is really
irrelevant at that point. You're you're
sub you're a slave to the market and
whoever will give you the money is going
to get a pound of flesh out of you
because they know they can. And you
know, it happens in the in the oil and
gas space all the time. I grew up in
Houston and literally there are guys in
town where you can point at him and go,
he goes bust at $10 a barrel, period.
Like, you know what his production costs
are, you know, and and and people try to
drive it down there to get him to puke
up their positions and they buy them on
the cheap. That's the game.
that that that Citadel story that situ
situational awareness guy is back in the
market now. It's it's kind of that news
has been out there. I guarantee you
>> you know that Citadel liquidated that
entire position within like two weeks
basically. I
>> I guarantee you Citadel is somehow
involved in making sure he's got a
little bit extra cra extra cash to get
back in the market. I guarantee you,
right? Because they're like, "Yeah, go
go go do it again." and they're like,
"Well, you know, if if he does well,
we've got a little percentage of this
and we'll do well, but if he does the
same thing, we get to do the same thing
again." Like, I g I guarantee you that
that that that's part of that trade. Um,
>> yeah, man. Finance is uh it's it's
endlessly interesting. Like, we can talk
about Bitcoin all we want. Um, but
markets are, man, the level of
resilience associated with the US
markets is is just unbelievable. just
absolutely unbelievable like you know
you know Patrick bet David you know 11
days ago oh it's going to be a bloody
Monday I can't believe what's going to
happen and were meaningfully higher from
when he sent out that tweet like it's
just you know yesterday I think the
markets added something like $1.5
trillion which is you know nearly the
market cap of Bitcoin in one day just
just one a one day move and it's not
like it was all over over the news, all
over the papers, all over, holy cow,
this is amazing, the biggest thing ever.
No, it was just a day in the markets. It
it's it really is extraordinary.
>> But that's why I think perspective and
history is so important for us to learn.
Like I grew up in a gold bug family. My
dad was a gold bug in since the 80s like
20% interest rate in the 80s. Like I
heard the whole narrative of Bitcoin
before Bitcoin was even invented. the
same arguments that all the Bitcoiners
made about fiat currency collapsing and
that whole crap. They act like they
invented that narrative and they
literally just repeated something from
40 years ago that has been the the fear
sells. To Gary's point earlier is like
buy the dips. Um, you know, fear are the
very dips that you're buying and they're
most of the time sha overshadowing the
the underlying truth that we have to
print more money to keep to stay in
power. Period. You have to service
future debt with cheaper dollars. That
is the way our economy works. And so you
look at how much money we're going to be
printing over the next decade. I think
that's why you're seeing, you know, kind
of a new price discovery happening
across commodities, across Bitcoin. And
yet we talk about all these surface
things as if the rising tide doesn't
float all ships. And the rising tide is
a 10-ft title wave coming in of
trillions of dollars of printed money
that no one in the world can convince me
is not going to be taken until we don't
have more guns than everybody else. Um,
and you know, our our US currency, no
matter how weak you think it is, show me
a better alternative. Show me where the
world wants to put money in the form of
paper that's more attractive than the US
government's form of it right now. I
don't think there is one. I don't think
that's going to be disrupted for a long
time because we have more consumer
>> Mhm.
>> We we have the best consumer demand of
any country that exists. We have the
largest economy of any country that ever
that exists. We're on the precipice of
the biggest AI boom that like we're
going to take the lead on all that. Why?
Well, because we're the innovators. Like
it doesn't matter
and we're the guys that know what to do
with the chips. So, all this is just
telling me, you know, it's just noise.
It's like everything's going to be more
expensive when we in 20 years than it is
now. Period. Everything. And Bitcoin, I
think, will catch more of that fever
than most other assets because it
doesn't have any cost to carry and you
can there's no in there's no scalable
problems that come with ownership.
Whereas there's a ton of scalable
problems that come with everything else.
Everything except for treasury bills.
That's literally it. Um
>> Tilman, I agree with everything you said
except one thing and it's a big one
which is everything will be more
expensive in 20 years. I think that's
really wrong. I think everything in the
next 5 to 10 years is going to be
extremely cheap.
Like, and here are examples. I can get
an M MBA from MIT today for nothing.
That is deflation by every absolutely
every definition. I have access to
people like yourselves before. I never
had access to you. I don't have to go
and stand in a convention for, you know,
30 days to get to the CEO of a company.
I It's like access is so much easier
today than it's ever been. If you have a
good story, a good pitch, and you're
articulate, it's impossible not to get
to whoever you want today. Nearly
impossible.
>> I would agree that there are going to be
a lot of things that go down in price.
You're right. Services, any technology,
any codebased product, anything like
that. I agree. But if you talk about
scarce hard assets, I I don't think
that's I I don't think
>> there isn't anything that's scarce. This
is
>> Bitco Bitcoin would be one example.
Gold, silver, houses, land, um all of
that.
>> Gold and silver at $4,500 gold, man.
They're making 60% margins.
>> Yeah. An oil producer selling crude oil
at $150 is making a 300% return on a
science. Now, this is no longer art,
dude. This is a big G700 flying
over Texas going, "Take some pictures.
Hey, we have 8,000 barrels of oil down
there. Go drill it." This is no longer a
guess, man. And prices,
>> it's not. But it still requires so so
much human labor attached. Prices go up
though, the capital pours into those
resources in volume, 300% return in oil
and gas. Everybody in their mother's
going to drill an oil well, right? I
mean, only the big guys are going to be
able to do it. To your point about
Americanism,
how you could short America at this
venture right here would be to me it's
insane because if you short America,
that means the whole world's in a
show. And we're the only country to date
who hasn't invested in its carpets.
Everyone we compete with, the sovereign
entity invests in their carpets. And
we've never done it. And I think that's
what Trump's going to put on absolute
jet fuel. And he's going to force the
401ks, the money market accounts. It's
it's all going to go into new
investments. And I to short this market
to me would be crazy to short America.
That's what I'm
>> That's really interesting because I've
seen all the headlines about Trump
wanting to do things like that about
reinvesting in our businesses and, you
know, nationalizing to some degree.
>> Well, he did it with Intel. He did it
with Intel. He did it. Yeah. He he, you
know, he never thought about the fact
that other countries have been doing
that for a long time. Like we've Why,
you know, that
>> China like crazy.
>> We cannot compete. All these Americans
that go, "Hey, we should not be buying
companies." You can't compete on a
global scale if you don't have Chinese
like Chinese companies have Chinese
sovereigns supporting them. So I could
easily see us taking 10% stakes in every
one of these companies or forcing the
Bank of America say hey get that
get the money out of money market
accounts and stick it into our
corporates. We want the stock market to
fly
>> and everyone's going to win, dude. If
you start getting
>> It would make it a lot more palatable if
they started buying Bitcoin in the
treasury in the strategic reserve if we
had a bunch of ownership of other things
and it was just a diversification play
versus like a you know I think that I
think you're spot on there. I hadn't
really thought about that. That's that's
a that's a that's a foreseeable future.
I think
>> you talk all about that. It's so
nonsensical to think about putting the
AI genie back in the bottle. Yeah. No,
there's no version of that.
>> You know, we need to slow down.
>> That's like having sex and then putting
a condom on later.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, seriously, right?
>> Feels better and you got to protect it.
>> That should be the quote for the month.
>> See, this is this is this is what this
is what you're going to get in Tampa if
Gary makes a trip to to our event. This
is the kind of dialogue you're going to
get with Arch Republic in in Tampa at
our
>> event.
Send it to your wife. She'll appreciate
the hum
cold storage, hot storage thing, you
know.
>> Yeah. There it is. There it is.
>> When it get to be 9:42 already. Hey
Gary, you want to see a video?
>> Sure. I'm going to show you the video of
the thing they're talking about cuz you
got to come here. I'm going to show you
guys a video cuz Arch Public's coming to
Tampa. Did you know this, Gary?
>> I didn't know it. When When y'all
coming?
>> October 15th, baby.
>> You want to throw a party?
>> Yeah. Look,
>> we are throwing a party. We are throwing
a party. We're bringing 250 of our
material.
>> Okay, I have enough
sweet.
>> Yeah. excited.
>> It's like a gajillionaire playground.
>> That was my voice in the thing. That was
weird.
>> Who said that?
>> Yep, that's it.
>> Yeah. Jerry,
have you been to the Motor Enclave yet?
>> No, I haven't.
>> Dude, that's sick. Can't wait.
>> Couple of our customers. Yeah, we're
gonna we're gonna host a full day there
from 8:30 to 8:30. Uh Gary, by the way,
I did DM you about our Tampa event like
two months ago saying, "Hey, we're
coming to Tampa. Do you want to be
involved?" No response. No, nothing.
Nothing from you. Got nothing.
>> Why don't you pick up the telephone,
Steve?
>> Well, you're right.
>> Yeah, you're right.
>> If you want to have a date with me,
call me on the telephone.
Too many actors online, dude. I don't
answer anything anymore. the DM.
the email.
>> So, uh,
>> I sent you a link to click on in your
DMs. You didn't click the link, Gary.
>> Don't check my DMs. I mean,
>> so, uh, no, we know how to get a hold of
me.
>> Yeah, knows.
>> Yeah, we absolutely want you there. We
We want you to be on stage with Scott.
He's going to host three hours of panels
in the middle of the day to start the
day. All of our clients and you and
anybody else that comes is going to
we're going to race cars around the
track uh and do some cool stuff there.
Uh the 1916 company uh which is the
world's largest watch retailer uh is
going to have $50 million of watches
there. Rolls-Royce is also going to be
there with a bunch of cars, you know, to
the right and left of the stage and at
other spots. So, it's going to be a
really, really, really cool, unique
event. Um, we want you there. Uh, bring
your
>> I can't believe you guys did invited me
two months ago cuz I would have said,
"Hey, let's do a party at the house
after or something." So, like,
>> we got a month. We've got a month to
still pull that off. Gary,
>> count me in, dude. Let's have a
Halloween party. I don't know. Do
something insane.
>> But count me in. And And I am a
customer, y'all. So, so I most certainly
get to go.
>> I probably need to react.
>> I love them. Yeah,
>> it it uh so um
>> did we lose Melker?
>> Yeah, Melker just lost power
>> and I lost audio for Andrew
>> Studio. Um so it's just you and I
talking the show's going to get better.
Watch this.
>> That's right.
>> They're changing the up. They're
bringing in the the southern boys and
the crazy people.
>> Oh yeah.
>> Million dollars worth of watches and and
fancy cars.
>> Yeah. No, exactly. Exactly.
>> It's going to be a lot of fun. We'll
we'll, you know, not only you and Scott
on stage, but I'm sure he'll bring some
other folks. Uh, it's
>> who is the show best designed for? Like,
who's the right customer? It
>> it's it's folks that, you know, um, have
meaningful capital. So, it's all of our
concierge clients, Gary. So, our top
1,000 clients out of our 30,000 users,
they're the ones that are invited to
this. So, we're going to have 250 to 300
people there. Um, so it's folks that
have a real interest in a couple of
things, you know, accumulating Bitcoin,
using Bitcoin products, but also using
our equity and ETF algorithms that we
launched two months ago to generate huge
amounts of cash flow that they can then
put back into Bitcoin if they want to.
Um, some of our systems and setups
around that have been just outrageous.
Well, this is a perfect example of what
Gary's already doing, but doing it
manually because he's an expert and he
knows what he's doing. But the the when
you see markets connect that have never
connected before. When you see the
opportunity to simultaneously play two
different symbols that are inversely
proportionate to one another in their
moves there creates an a a arbitrage
opportunity in the volatility attached
to those two assets like you've never
seen before. And so I look at it as like
I give the analogy all the time. It's
like volatility is like rainfall. It's
really hard to predict and the further
out you try to predict it, the harder it
is. But you know, rainfall happens
everywhere sometimes. You know, water,
if you're going to put buckets to try to
catch rain in New Orleans, well, then
you're relying on Gulf systems to
produce that moisture. If you're going
to put buckets in California, you're
going to be looking at Nino
type crops that El Nino. But my wrong
this year again,
>> my point my point is is like all of
these areas have different drivers for
moisture and different drivers that
produce the rain. And so in the age of
AI and in the age of automation, I think
the volatility potential or the
volatility yield potential attached to
the markets and the ability to catch
that volatility is the first time in
human history that we've been very very
close or have arrived at systematic
advantage attached to compounding. Like
when you can make a quarter percent clip
every single day across the markets for
volatility, you're harnessing a power
that you've never harnessed before. And
Einstein calls it the eighth wonder of
the world, the most powerful force in
nature, which is the laws of
compounding. And I don't think most
people understand what that looks like.
And I think if you play volatility traps
across the markets and you do it
according to how proportionate they are
in their moves, if they're inverse, then
there are little arbitrage opportunities
that will yield those types of results.
And if you can do that every single day,
you will be richer than any of your
wildest dreams. And that's something
that's never been available to us
before. We're knocking on that door. And
so my point to people is is like if
volatility is good and you can set traps
buckets to catch it, wouldn't you want
buckets in as many cities as you can and
all you're doing at that point is
adjusting the size of the buckets based
upon the average rainfall? Like there's
no reason to have a massive bucket in
the desert because it doesn't ring them.
And all eventually investing to me is
going to be all about how well you
harvest the volatility across all of the
markets. How much rain can you catch
every single day across these different
fronts and across the systems that are
moving? And you can't do that manually,
period. And so that's where I think we
we we're at the nexus of something
really really special.
>> Well, you can do it manually, but you've
got to be a hedge fund that employs, you
know, 57 people sitting across trading
desks, you know, spending all day
attempting to do it manually.
>> Well, you can do it manually against one
market like that. It's like Gary's done
it exceptionally well. He he I'd love
for you to go through kind of what you
did on that trade, but you you did it.
You took a cash yielding focused product
and combined it with a huge upside gains
profit or product and you said okay I'm
going to have the middle ground. I want
the best of both worlds. I want my money
every month like a selling of covered
call strategy would give me the rich
man's game but I also want a bunch of
upside potential on the back end of it
too. That doesn't show me another asset
class where that's actually even existed
at the same time.
>> Yeah, really true. You know, I've
actually probably underutilized my my
ability on my position because I you
know, I've been studying Bitcoin. I
didn't want to lose it. I didn't want to
do anything stupid. Um
but you know, you you guys talk about
volatility is vitality. I I don't think
for most people that's true. I think
volatility
>> Gary, I lost audio on you. I can't hear
you at all right now. I don't really I
saw your mouth say vital v uh volatility
is vitality. And I did see that online,
but let me I'm afraid to jump back out
because I don't think Scott will let me
back in. I think he got kicked.
>> Yeah, and we lost Andrew.
>> Andrew, I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
Yeah, I can hear you, Tilman. No
problem.
>> Can you hear me?
>> I can hear you just fine. Yep.
>> So, Tilman's got the problem. But what I
was saying is that I think I don't think
>> I got it back. I'm back.
>> The reason I went into STRC wasn't
because I was brilliant. It was because
I was confused a year ago in October,
November of last year when the market
just went
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't understand any of
this. Okay. If I don't understand it and
I've missed, you know, I've lost a lot
of opportunities and making lots of
money. But if if I don't understand it,
I can't I'm not going to go to bed at
night and feel comfortable. I'm I'm
going to be like, why did I chase? Oh,
Scott Melker told me to buy. Like,
that's not a reason to buy Okay. I
mean, it's I'm better off listening to
somebody on the street. I mean, I just
>> Yeah.
>> Um, so for me, the volatility for most
people in the audience, I don't think it
is vitality. I think it's fear. And that
allowed me to go sit the money at
$94,000 Bitcoin. And I'd already bought
some 102. In fact, I did some with you
guys in the hund. I said, "Hey, let's
let's go into Gemini and let's deploy
your tool." And you did a great job. But
I was like, "Hey, do I really want to
buy some more $100,000 Bitcoin?"
>> Right? This is the thing for Bitcoin to
me. No one should chase Bitcoin ever
again. It is a lie.
>> It is a lie that $300 Bitcoiners are
telling you. They are average cost is
300 bucks, dude. And they're telling you
to buy any level, but they're not. I am
not going to buy $120,000 Bitcoin. I'm
not doing it, dude. I'm going to wait
for it to come back to me
>> and I'm probably not going to buy 95s
because I think I'm still going to see
in the 70s again. This product wants to
shake people out, man. It really wants
to shake people out.
>> What tools allow you to do that?
>> And to Andrew's point earlier, the vi
the the volatility attached to leverage
trading will keep the market honest for
a very forever because there's too much
money that can be gained with too little
capital placed in order for those trades
not to be taken. That's why you see, you
know, these headlines every time Bitcoin
moves. What's the major headline?
Everybody says this many shorts
liquidated at this price or this many
longs. That's all that's all leveraged
money. That's all people going I can
put, you know, $10 in and get $200
represented. I get 20 to one leverage in
some of these cases. Like, why wouldn't
I take small bets, you know, when I
think it's the bottom? because it can
pay 20 to1 on it can pay 20% yield on a
1% move even if I'm slightly right you
know I can get a lot of money that that
that is going to continue the
degenerates are always going to want to
try to harness that volatility for quick
getrich money and that you can you can
be a sucker and fall into that game or
you can play the stupid simple like
volatility is an asset but you only buy
on the big red candles if If you really
look at what you It's really simple.
Don't chase green candles, which means
don't start buying after you see them.
Chase the big red candles DCA into those
and you're going to be really happy one
day. And other if you don't, you're
still going to have the best exposure to
the cost curve that you could get in the
asset. So, you may be wrong in your
thesis. You may be wrong. Bitcoin could
go to zero one day, but you're not wrong
in the way you've played the cards.
Gary, I know you're a card player. Do
you ever leave a poker tournament where
you have the nuts on the turn and you go
all in and someone draws you out on the
river and you go, "Damn it, I shouldn't
have done that." No, you had the nuts.
You You played it perfectly.
>> Everything on that trade. And it's like,
"Hey, I still should have." Now, maybe I
shouldn't have maybe I got in over my
head, but uh like when you have a
chance, when the fast ball's coming
down, you swing at the ball, dude. You
don't for a better pitch. Swing at the
damn ball. My god. Just
>> Well, and to your point, just don't
enter tournaments where if you get
knocked out, you're broke. You know, if
the buy into the tournament is too rich,
that's where you make the decision. But
you don't make the decision at the table
like you're scared money. Like, oh, this
guy's pushed all in on me and you've got
the nuts and you're scared to call them.
That tells you you the buyin was too
rich for you, man. You can't you're
playing with money you can't afford to
lose. Whereas, if you're in a healthy,
you know, ratio to your net worth,
you're just going, man, I played that
hand great. Luck wasn't for me. It went
against me. I got knocked out, but I did
it exact. I'd do it a hundred times the
same way again and I probably would win
won 90 of the tournaments. You know,
that's the way that's the way real
investors think in my in my opinion. And
that's very different than the way
Bitcoin investors think. Very different.
Um
>> yeah,
>> they think like my 15year-old son does,
>> right?
>> That they're the luckiest people in the
room all the time. And they play the
hands like that. Like, oh, I'm I'm I got
a 16% chance of winning. I'm that guy,
you know?
That's the way I play blackjack in
Vegas. Yeah, that's the way I play
blackjack in Vegas. I'm the luckiest guy
at the table. Let's go all in on 13. I'm
I'm sticking I'm sticking on 13.
Well, uh we can uh stay on the stream
here and just stare at each other uh for
another few minutes or you know,
>> let me ask you a question before we go.
Um, where do you guys think this thing
hits resistance and really starts to
struggle? Um, I made a comment about,
hey, I think we could see 70s. I think
it'd be healthy. Not necessary, but I
think it would be healthy to see a
retracement and just see another grab at
mid70s, low 70s. Um, you know, and that
may be spurred by a nuclear incident or
a radiation event or a sunspot moment or
who knows. This world is so insane.
>> It It's hard to say because we
>> I'm looking for a $17,000 pullback
before I even think about something
because I'm I'm of the firm belief that
you always look for a 50% retracement
and the bounce. And so we've gone up
40%. I want to see a 20% pullback. And
when I see the 20% pullback and I see a
rounding bottom on the 20% and I see
volume step in and I see a confirmation,
to me that's the most riskless entry
that you can get. Um it doesn't mean
that it won't
>> 7275ish.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's where that's where
I'm thinking because I think 75 was a
material point uh in our Bitcoin
history. It's reached that
>> beautiful the other day, dude.
And so I'd be looking for it to hold
again after a major pull back because if
it if it does then you have a very
you've got a higher percentage
likelihood that that's actually the
bottom where it's going to bounce. And
it doesn't mean the permanent bottom. It
just means the bottom for that leg of
the journey on you know that that
volatility lag essentially. Um I bet
with my brother and some other guy for
um I said look we see 75 and I was
really nervous of the bet. We'll see
75,000 before we see 817.
It's a week ago. Happened in two days.
Grant had to pay me off.
But but you know, when it hits 75,000,
it was really a bad bet on me. I should
have said 75800 or something. It hit
75,000 and it just pierced right below
it.
>> It stayed there for two seconds, man.
>> I mean, maybe 20 seconds. Okay. And
these people that are sitting there
going, "Hey, I'm waiting for the
bottom." Dude, if your bid isn't already
there, you ain't getting hit. You're
going to be lucky to get hit if it's
there,
>> right? If you put in 94.99, right? You
you you like it's these these very
bottom marks don't last very long.
>> No. And they squeeze away from you
really, really, really fast. Really
fast. Like you go from that 748 up to 76
in less than an hour. I mean, you it it
moves really fast on you. Um, yeah, it's
it's uh yeah, if we see a retracement,
great. I don't think it'll be a quote
unquote violent retracement. I don't
think that's how Bitcoin moves anymore.
I don't think we're going to see a down
6% day, you know, anytime soon. Again,
we're we're back in the the fall, right?
Sell and go away is over. It's been over
for a month. We're back in this space
now where people are making allocations
to portfolios
um that are, you know, let's call it the
bid underneath Bitcoin in a much much
bigger way than it was over the past 6
months. Um so, you know, we we may get
back there, but it it it would be a a
slow bleed of some sort. Um I don't
know. I I you know, un
we'll see. It'll probably clip to 70s.
How deep it goes into the 70s, I'm not
entirely sure. There there's when I'm
seeing Morgan Stanley, you know, double
the highest day they've ever had, that
just tells me something. That just tells
me that the narrative is starting to
grab hold uh in spaces that, you know,
those people aren't going to sell their
Bitcoin. No matter what it does, you
know, on a day-to-day ba basis, they are
never going to sell. And those people
have been taught for the past 20 years,
if you purchase an asset because you've
made a decision that you believe in its
long-term viability,
any dip of any kind is for buying, add
money to that position. So again, that's
a that's another bid that's just kind of
sitting there, right? That that that's
really hard to break. So we'll see. If
we see 75 over the next 90 days, I'd be
slightly surprised. I'd be I'd be a
little bit surprised. Yeah.
>> Well, I will just say this. I I think
that the the guard has changed
officially, and I think whatever bottoms
we find are Wall Street bottoms, like
you said, systematic buys. Um, and it's
I if you look at like old school
Bitcoiners, the hardcore narrative guys,
they've moved to Zcash. Um, and that's
why Zcash has gone crazy. Um, they the
narrative that they are married to
doesn't exist in Bitcoin anymore. They
want they want the the anarchist coin.
They want to feel like the rest of the
world's collapsing and they're the
smartest people in the room that have
the only asset that's going to survive.
I just think it's just incredibly naive,
very childlike, very foolish. Um, and
we're going to we're going to see this
is the first time in the Bitcoin's
history that we've actually seen that
take place. The capitulation from the
OGs act actually come home to they've
sold out a lot of those coins. And I
don't, to Andrew's point, I don't think
the people that bought those coins are
nearly as price sensitive or capital
sensitive as the people that sold them.
And I think that that's going to be a
material difference as it pertains to
where the future price goes. You know,
if you look at the regular stock market,
for example, one of the greatest secrets
that nobody really thinks about is not
only that inflation drives prices up,
but every employee in America is buying
US securities every day with their 401k.
There is a literal bid. There's a bid
floor at plus 1% of the average daily
volume. There's more. There's 1% of
every day's volume on the bid
>> every single day, whether you like it or
not, whether people are feeling good
about it or not, because people are at
their jobs and their money managers are
shoveling their money into Google. And
we're going to see that grow over the
next 10 years in Bitcoin. and 1% of that
pi pushed into Bitcoin is gonna have a a
huge net effect on the price compared to
all the other markets. Uh it's just a
much smaller market. It's going to move
it more in my opinion.
>> Well, I think that's an awesome way to
close. I mean, what else can we say?
>> That's dope.
That's dope.